<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Middle Class Capital</title>
    <link>https://middleclass.capital/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Middle Class Capital</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://middleclass.capital/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our 2023 Predictions</title>
      <link>https://middleclass.capital/articles/2023_predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://middleclass.capital/articles/2023_predictions/</guid>
      <description>Dereek  The bottom is in COIN gonna outperform BTC Shangai is gonna cause a 2-3 day caos where the majority of liquid staking derivatives die and a couple grow their market share even more. The net flow of staked eth is gonna be positive (more deposit than withdraws) Maker is gonna baloon up in revenue but the token will keep underperforming US Core CPI peaked and will come down. but won&amp;rsquo;t go under 4% wstETH contract will hold more than 50% of all stETH we get more than one Gamefi hit in the normie world More widespread NFT adoption under the digital collectibles name  Serendipity  Gamefi continues to be trash until all crypto notions are abstracted (not happening 2023) Artblocks keeps making more random bullshit: it sells anyway BTC makes another low, but never beyond 12k Crypto continues to be integrated into high-profile websites/services (like reddit); market doesn&amp;rsquo;t really care beyond temporary pumps in respective coins First modular blockchain stacks with mainnet release; creates temporary &amp;lsquo;modular blockchain&amp;rsquo; season stETH plebs achieve sweet, sweet freedom; reflect that locking up your funds for months has a terrible opportunity cost indeed Portugal implements legislation to tax crypto, with mandatory reporting of exchanges to the state for any balances over X minimum amount Trading gets noticeably harder; those without dedication are squeezed out and capitulate  Target  Crypto overall - less volatile, slowly ranging, but might go lower before going higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A not so Miner problem</title>
      <link>https://middleclass.capital/articles/miner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://middleclass.capital/articles/miner/</guid>
      <description>How unprofitable miners have turned towards high APY loan sharks and put the industry at risk for another contagion event</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The power of Community</title>
      <link>https://middleclass.capital/articles/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://middleclass.capital/articles/community/</guid>
      <description>The glue that holds a project together is its community. Memes, community projects and die-hard believers are all good signs of a strong community. This is especially important for projects that have “no intrinsic value” and are mostly fueled about speculation, like NFT pfp collections or meme coins. Having a strong community is a value of itself, and it also means a big percentage of the supply is basically locked forever, held by people that will never sell.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
